# Adil Shehzad

## Jr. DevOps Engineer, Community Builder

Always been a thriller person who gets the work done on time and with perfection. Worked on Linux, Python, JavaScript, Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Terraform (IaC), Kubernetes RedHat Openshift, Redis, and Serverless Cloud Computing Using AWS Lambda, I am also able to lead and promote a wide variety of community programs and activities to audiences of all ages and ethnic backgrounds.

adil.shehzad4146@gmail.com

+923084146744

Lahore, Pakistan 👂

adilshehzad786.github.io/

linkedin.com/in/adilshehzad7 in

live:iamad1l (S)

github.com/adilshehzad786

stackoverflow.com/users/12373865/adil-shehzad

medium.com/@adilshehzad786

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Computer Science** University of Central Punjab

09/2017 - 07/2021

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **DevOps Automation Engineer**

Systems Limited

07/2021 - Present Lahore

## Software Developer Grey Software, Canada

02/2021 - 04/2021

Remote Work

Achievements/Tasks

- Creating Web Application Using JavaScript, Redux **NuxtJS and ReactJS**
- Automation Tasks of GitHub & GitLab using GitHub Actions, Gitlab Ci and N8N
- Web Development using NuxtJS and VueJS
- Opensource Contribution on Projects
- Handling Netlify and AWS Servers

Contact: arsala bangash - Ex-Google Employee

## Terraform Cloud Intern

Microtechx

Lahore, Pakistan

09/2020 - 01/2021 Achievements/Tasks

- Created Azure Hybrid Identity Project
- Docker & Kubernetes Deployment on Azure
- Zero Trust Deployment

## Software Quality Assurance (SQA) Afiniti

06/2020 - 09/2020

Lahore, Pakistan

Achievements/Tasks

- Testing and Debugging Software's.
- Reporting Software to the relevant authority.
- Team Leader in Software Quality Department for testing and development of software's.

## **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

ResumeMate (02/2020 - Present)

ResumeMate provides professional assistance with a premium template resume. ResumeMate is a non-profit Web Application That Saved User Data on Microsoft Azure Blob, Container and has the ability to Creates a Shareable resume link with a complete userlevel Control panel. ResumeMate has ReactJS Frontend and Django Python Backend.

#### COMMUNITIES

GitHub Docs Team (Moderator) (05/2021 - Present) Managing GitHub Docs on GitHub

GitHub Stream Team (04/2021 - Present)

Creating Educational Stuffs for GitHub Education Community.

GitHub Campus Expert (11/2020 - Present)

Building GitHub Community in Pakistan

AWS User Group Lahore Lead (06/2020 - 04/2021)

Leading Cloud Computing Technologies from Pakistan

### CERTIFICATES

Chaos Engineering Practitioner (06/2021 - Present)

GitLab Certified Associate (06/2021 - Present)

Scrum Foundation Certified (05/2021 - Present)

Aviatrix MultiCloud Engineer (01/2021 - 01/2024)

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Urdu

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### INTERESTS

Coding Traveling **Reading Books** 

Swimming